https://www.beavercreekflorist.com/privacy.htm

2173 N. Fairfield Rd.
Privacy
We know that you care how your information is used, and we appreciate your
trust that we will use it carefully and sensibly. This notice describes our
privacy policy. By visiting us, you are accepting the privacy policy
described below.
1.  What Personal Information Do We Collect?
Information You Provide.
We
receive and store information you enter.  For example, when you
search for or buy a product or service, or when you supply information
such as your address, phone number or credit card. You can choose not to
provide certain information, but then you might not be able to take
advantage of some of our features.  We use the information that you
provide for such purposes as responding to your requests, customizing
future shopping for you, improving our website, and communicating with
you.  In addition, if you choose, we may share your information with
other companies who provide goods or services that you are interested
in.  Please see the “opt-in/opt-out” selection in Section 4 of this
policy.
Cookies.
Like many
websites, we use "cookies".  Cookies are small programs
that we transfer to your hard drive that allow us to recognize you and to
provide you with a customized shopping experience.  If you do not
want us to use cookies, you can easily disable them by going to the
toolbar of your web browser, and clicking on the “help” button.
Follow the instructions that will prevent the browser from accepting
cookies, or set the browser to inform you when you receive a new
cookie.  In addition, you may visit this and other websites
anonymously through the use of utilities provided by other private
companies.
Other Information:
Every
computer has an IP (Internet Protocol) address.  IP addresses of
computers used to visit this site are noted.  In addition, we automatically
collect other information such as email addresses, browser types,
operating systems, and the URL addresses of sites clicked to and from this
site.
Information from Other
Sources.
We might receive information about you from other
sources and add it to our account information.  This may include
updated delivery and address information from our shippers or other
sources so that we can correct our records and deliver your next purchase
or communication more easily.
2.  How Do We Use Your
Information?
Customized Shopping.  We use your information to better serve you by providing a customized
shopping experience.  As noted above, you may “opt-out” of this
customization, or even visit and shop anonymously.
Agents. We employ
other companies and individuals to perform functions on our behalf.
Examples include delivering packages, sending postal mail and e-mail, and
processing credit card payments. They have access to personal information
needed to perform their functions, but may not use it for other purposes.
Special Offers.
We may send you special offers from time to time, unless you choose to
“opt-out” of receiving such offers.  In addition, we may also send
you special offers from other companies.  Again, you may
“opt-out”.  If we send you offers from other businesses, we do not
share your personal information with them.  The offers come directly
through us.  Please see the “opt-in/opt-out” selection at the end of
this policy.
Business Transfers. As
we continue to develop our business, we might sell or buy stores or
assets. In such transactions, customer information generally is one of the
transferred business assets. Also, in the unlikely event that we are
acquired, customer information will be one of the transferred assets.
Law
Enforcement.   If we receive a lawful court order to release
account or other personal information then we will comply with the
law.  We will also release information when necessary to protect the
life, safety or property of others. This includes exchanging information with
other companies and organizations for fraud protection and credit risk
reduction.
3.  How Do We Protect the
Security of Your Information?
We work to protect the
security of your information during transmission by using Secure Sockets
Layer (SSL) software, which encrypts information you input.
We use encryption to protect
your information contained in our customer list.
We use a firewall to protect
against unlawful intrusion.
We limit access to your
information on a “need to know” basis.
We reveal only the last five
digits of your credit card numbers when confirming an order. Of course, we
transmit the entire credit card number to the appropriate credit card
company during order processing.
It is important for you to
protect against unauthorized access to your password and to your computer.
Be sure to sign off when finished using a shared computer.
No system can guarantee
absolute security, just as the finest lock can not guarantee physical
security.  However, we take every reasonable precaution to assure
that your data is secure.
4.
Your Choice:  Opt-in or Opt-out.
It is your choice
whether to receive emails or special offers from us or others.  The
following section provides you with this choice.  Please note the default
settings.
·
Please send me email or other mail informing me of special offers of
your products or services.
·
Please do not send me email or other mail informing me of special offers
of your products or services.
·
Please send me email or other mail informing me of special offers of
related products or services from other companies.
·
Please do not send me email or other mail informing me of special offers
of related products or services from other companies.
5.  Children
We do not sell products or services to children. If you
are under 18, you may use this site only with involvement of a parent or
guardian.
6.  Other Websites
Various Web sites may be linked to from this site.
If you link to another site, your privacy depends on the policy of that
site.  We strongly urge you to check their privacy policy.  Not all
sites guarantee that they will not share your personally identifiable
information with others.  You may also wish to consult privacy guidelines
such as those recommended by the Online Privacy Alliance (www.privacyalliance.org).
7.  Contact Us
If you would like to learn more about our privacy
policy, or to access your personally identifiable information contained on our
website, you may contact us at 937-426-4253. You will be required to provide
identifier information to assure that this information is not released to
others.  We reserve the right to modify this policy in the future.
If we do so, notice will be posted on our home page.
(888) 216-4253
Beavercreek, Ohio. For 40 years, fresh flowers delivered daily in the surrounding Dayton, OH area.
Beavercreek Florist provides quality flowers, arrangements, and gifts for all special occasions like birthdays, get well and sympathy flowers. We send for residential, business, hospital, and funeral home delivery. Trust Beavercreek Florist to have just the right floral arrangement for you.
The experienced designer’s at Beavercreek Florist are here to create beautiful flower arrangements for your occasion. Every bouquet is meticulously designed with fresh flowers, and then hand-delivered to your recipient’s door by our experienced and friendly delivery staff.
Depend on Beavercreek Florist for beautiful flowers, gifts and candy that are a luxury at any price. Browse the Beavercreek Florist website and order online, or call our shop in and speak with our friendly staff.
Florist Website Design by Media99
